<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>RISSQ</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on RISSQ</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Project contributors</title>
      <link>/people/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/people/</guid>
      <description>Principal Investigator Emilio L. Cano
 Internships Manu Alfaro
Juan
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project supporters</title>
      <link>/supporters/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/supporters/</guid>
      <description>Companies Thanks to Luc Castermans, Developer Manager at Signify (former Philips Lighting) for providing a letter of interest.
 Academic  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RISSQ Packages</title>
      <link>/packages/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/packages/</guid>
      <description>Common infrastructure Common structures, classes
Data sets
Shiny App
Input/Output interfaces: file import, export, etc.
 Statistical methods Statistical Process Control: Control Charts, Capability Analysis
Measurement Systems Analysis: Type I, Crossed, Nested, Unbalanced
Acceptance Sampling
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RISSQ Project</title>
      <link>/project/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/</guid>
      <description>The Problem Industry and Business need Statistics for their survival and development. Being this an axiom difficult to contradict, and having the statistical software R had an impressive increase of use1, it would be expected that statistical methods for quality control and improvement had had a similar evolution. However, even though some companies are starting to use R for those methods, there is a long way to attain the usage and confidence standard commercial tools have reached2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>This is the website for the RISSQ project (R Infrastructure for Statistical Standards on Quality). The project was started by the author of the SixSigma R package author, Emilio L. Cano1. Check the updated list of supporters and contributors.
 Emilio L. Cano, Statistician. Associate Professor at the Faculty of Law and Social Sciences of the University of Castilla-la Mancha (UCLM), as well as research scientist at the Institute for Regional Development (IDR) of the UCLM.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>